<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">LowVisCam</string>
    <string name="image_gallery">Image Gallery</string>
    <string name="action_switch_contrast">Switch Contrast</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="button_reverse_cam">Reverse Camera</string>
    <string name="button_capture">Capture</string>
    <string name="button_share">Share</string>
	<string name="action_gallery">Image Gallery</string>
	<string name="action_about">About</string>
	<string name="share_using">Share using</string>
	<string name="ok">OK</string>
	<string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
	<string name="search_results">Search Results</string>
	<string name="action_search">Search</string>
	<string name="search_hint">Search images</string>
	<string name="view_image">View Image</string>
	
	
	<string name="dialog_title">About LowVisCam</string>
	<string name="dialog_message">
	    Welcome to LowVisCam. LowViscam is a camera application specifically 
	    designed for low vision and blind users. LowViscam is designed to allow 
	    visually impaired persons the ability to frame their friends or themselves 
	    in pictures using face detection software. In order to utilize the full functionality 
	    of the face detection software, please use headphones while using this app. 
	    You will receive audio feedback depending on the position of the face in the 
	    camera frame. The farther left or right the face is in the frame, the more beeps you will 
	    hear. The farther up or down the face is in the frame, the higher or lower the 
	    pitch of those beeps will be. Beeps will also play in the left or right channels 
	    of the headphones depending on the left or right positioning of the face. 
	    For example, if a head is in the bottom left corner, you will hear 3 low pitch 
	    beeps in the left headphone. If a head is positioned in the center on top you 
	    will hear 1 high pitch beep in both headphones. A face in the perfect center will 
	    receive a separate ding noise. Multiple faces in frame are calculated by the middle 
	    point of all faces. 
	    
	    The image gallery is accessible by the image gallery button on the action bar. Each image 
	    in the image gallery has two actions. A long click will open the share options for the 
	    image. A single click will open that image in the image viewer. Left and 
	    right swipes in the image viewer will show your other images.

		There are two themes available for LowVisCam, white background with black text, and 
		black background with yellow text. If at any time you want to change the 
		theme, select the \'Switch Contrast\' button in the action overflow button.
			    
	    Simple enough right? You\'ll get used to it the more you use LowViscam. Have fun 
	    taking pictures!
	    
	</string>
	
</resources>
